Guide to the Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC records, 1980-2013 MS2230
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- 2015 donation materials, 1981-2013; MS2230 Series 7
  - Marketing, development, and production records, 1984-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3
    - 1983-1984 programs, news articles, fan mail, seating charts, invoices, newsletters, financial statements, board applications, audition forms [3/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - 1983-1984 programs, news articles, fan mail, seating charts, invoices, newsletters, financial statements, board applications, audition forms [4/4], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Metro Weekly, 2006 May-June; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, marketing materials, Board minutes, season brochure, 2005, 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Communications, marketing, grant applications, concert programs, Board minutes [COM/MARK COM 06/07] [1/2], 2006-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Communications, marketing, grant applications, concert programs, Board minutes [COM/MARK COM 06/07] [2/2], 2006-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - 25th Anniversary History of GMCW, Spring Affair, news articles, 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Festival literature, Board applications, "We Are One" gig sheet & music, Board rosters, draft budgets, marketing materials, development workshop materials, Board materials, Board meetings, financial statements, Executive Director search [1/4], 2007-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Festival literature, Board applications, "We Are One" gig sheet & music, Board rosters, draft budgets, marketing materials, development workshop materials, Board materials, Board meetings, financial statements, Executive Director search [2/4], 2007-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Festival literature, Board applications, "We Are One" gig sheet & music, Board rosters, draft budgets, marketing materials, development workshop materials, Board materials, Board meetings, financial statements, Executive Director search [3/4], 2007-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Festival literature, Board applications, "We Are One" gig sheet & music, Board rosters, draft budgets, marketing materials, development workshop materials, Board materials, Board meetings, financial statements, Executive Director search [4/4], 2007-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Capital Circle, newsletters, fan mail, minutes [Marketing Plan 07], 2007, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Grants [Devo Com 07/08], 2007-2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Development materials [Dev. Comm. 06/07], 2006-2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Barbara Cook reception [B. Cook Event 06], 2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Concert planning materials, advertising contracts, corporate sponsorships, Food & Friends volunteering [Program Advertising], 2001, 2007, 2009, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Sponsors [1/2], 2000, 2001, 2005, 2006, 2009, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Sponsors [2/2], 2000, 2001, 2005, 2006, 2009, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Sponsors [1/2], 2001-2006, 2010-2012, undated; Series 7 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Sponsors [2/2], 2001-2006, 2010-2012, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Sponsors, 2000-2001, 2003-2007; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - DC Commissions of Arts & Humanities (DCCAH) [1/3], 2002-2006, 2008, 2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - DC Commissions of Arts & Humanities (DCCAH) [2/3], 2002-2006, 2008, 2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - DC Commissions of Arts & Humanities (DCCAH) [3/3], 2002-2006, 2008, 2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Sponsor materials, 2009-2012; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - DC Commissions of Arts & Humanities [1/2], 1999-2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - DC Commissions of Arts & Humanities [2/2], 1999-2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Brother Help Thyself, BHT newsletters [Grants and Funding], 1998-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Grants [1/3], 2002, 2006-20014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Grants [2/3], 2002, 2006-2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Grants [3/3], 2002, 2006-2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts [NEA Funding], 2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - DC Lottery [DC Lottery sponsorship], 2008; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - DCCAH grants [DCCAH Diversity Series], 2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - DCCAH grants [1/3], 2008-2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - DCCAH grants [2/3], 2008-2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - DCCAH grants [3/3], 2008-2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - United Way, Form 990 [1/2], 2004-2007, 2009-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - United Way, Form 990 [2/2], 2004-2007, 2009-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - CFC & United Way applications [1/2], 2003-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - CFC & United Way applications [2/2], 2003-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - United Arts Organization of Greater Washington [1/2], 2000-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - United Arts Organization of Greater Washington [2/2], 2000-2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Brother Help Thyself, grant materials, 1999-2000, 2003-2005, 2007, 2010-2011, 2013-2014; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Jennifer Holiday [Holliday] contract [2010-2011 season], 2008, 2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Concert recordings [2009-2010 season] [Grease CDs], MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Fundraising campaign, FY11 Board pledges, Board materials, reports, minutes, 2010-2011; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Planned giving workshop (web-based), 2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Fundraising workshop, season brochure, sponsorship materials, Capital Circle, corporate sponsorships, strategic planning, development materials [1/3], 2003-2004, 2006-2007, 2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising workshop, season brochure, sponsorship materials, Capital Circle, corporate sponsorships, strategic planning, development materials [2/3], 2003-2004, 2006-2007, 2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Fundraising workshop, season brochure, sponsorship materials, Capital Circle, corporate sponsorships, strategic planning, development materials [3/3], 2003-2004, 2006-2007, 2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising correspondence, Everett Waldo memorial CD, 2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Capital Club roster, correspondence, Ovation Society material, planned giving audit, 2001, 2009, 2011-2013; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Grant prospects & correspondence [Foundation/Grant Prospects] [1/2], 1995, 2002-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Grant prospects & correspondence [Foundation/Grant Prospects] [2/2], 1995, 2002-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Jim Richardson recording endowment fund, Bob Wonneberger Fund, 1986, 200-2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Audiovisual materials, 1982-2006; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4
    The original order of the 2015 donation has been maintained throughout Series 7 and its subseries. The arrangement of the Audiovisual subseries follows the organization of the boxes when they were donated.
    The materials in this subseries contain video and audio cassette tape recordings of Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, DC performances. The materials date from 1982 to 2006.
    For additional audiovisual materials, please see Series 5.
    - Video cassettes, GMCW performances, 1988-1992, 1995-1999, 2001; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 55)
    - Video cassettes, GMCW performances, 1986, 1988-1992, 1994-1995, 1997, 2000-2003, 2006, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 57)
    - Cassette Tapes, 1982, 1990-1991; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Cassette Tapes, 1988; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Cassette Tapes, 1991-1992, 1994; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Cassette Tapes, undated; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - CDs, 1999-2000; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Video cassettes, GMCW performances, 1988-1992, 1995-1997, 2004; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 71-A)
  - Photographs, MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 5
  - Ovation Society development material, planned giving, 2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Ovation Society material [Estate of Henry B. Powers], 1997; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Jim Richardson recording endowment fund, 1996-1997; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - New Century Circle Fund pledges, Century Circle Investment policy, financial statements, 2001-2002; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Fundraising workshop materials, database management material [ETapestry Donor Program], 2003; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Major Gifts program (2005), advertising contracts (2010), annual reports (1988-1999), Metro Weekly (2009), database material, newsletters (2008), Corporate Circle, 2008-2009 Season Brochure, 1999, 2005-2006, 2008-2010; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - 2005 Catalog of Philanthropy & related material, 2004-2005; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous material [Capital Club, development and grant material, 2005 Form 990, 2006 Financial statements, Meyer Foundation materials, Gelman Library press release, member roster] [1/2], 2001, 2005-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    Original folder title provided by the donor: "Miscellaneous material: Development Circle, major gifts program, Spring Affair material, proposed budget (2005-2006), Capital Club roster (2001), Gelman Library proposal, press release, & deed of gift (2007), Logo material (2008), IRS Application for 501(c)(3) (1982), financial statements (2006 & 2009), Form 990 (2005), Planned Giving estate (1998), Barbara Cook concert program (2006), advertising contracts (2006-2007), major gifts program (2005), Multi years" This title was edited during the 2022 processing as it appears not all of these items were included in the original folder.
  - Miscellaneous material [Capital Club, development and grant material, 2005 Form 990, 2006 Financial statements, Meyer Foundation materials, Gelman Library press release, member roster] [2/2], 2001, 2005-2009; MS2230 Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous materials [Kennedy Center, ETapestry emails, DCAH FY08, James Holloway commissioned music fund, J Richardson endowment fund, Stepanek, Multi years; Series 7 (Box UP22, Folder 20)
    Miscellaneous material: Concert program (2003), Ken Cen concert material (2003), database material (no year), DCCAH (FY08), endowments (2009), Capital Circle contributions (2009), matching pledges (2004), James Holloway Commissioned Music Fund (2000), Jim Richardson Endowment Fund (2006), Jim Richardson Recording Endowment Fund (1996), performing rights correspondence (2003)
  - Development material, 2004; Series 7 (Box UP22, Folder 21)
  - Matching gifts programs, corporate fundraising, 2000-2001; Series 7 (Box UP22, Folder 22)
  - National Arts Marketing Project (NAMP), marketing materials, 2005-2007; Series 7 (Box UP22, Folder 23)
  - Concerts, minutes, financials, 1982-1983; Series 7 (Box UP23, Folder 1)
  - Budget, financials, 1987; Series 7 (Box UP23, Folder 2)
  - Budget, minutes, financials, Board elections, 1993-1994; Series 7 (Box UP23, Folder 3)
  - Membership requirements, financials, committee charges, budget, 1981-1983; Series 7 (Box UP23, Folder 4)
  - Financials, budget, 1985; Series 7 (Box UP23, Folder 5)
  - Board meeting agenda, committee reports, Board meeting minutes, 1983; Series 7 (Box UP23, Folder 6)
  - Financials, roster, Articles of Incorporation (1981), by-laws, Form 990, minutes, proposed concerts & music, newsletters, March on Washington material, 1986-1987; Series 7 (Box UP23, Folder 7)
  - Financials, 1984; Series 7 (Box UP24, Binder 1)
  - Board correspondence, minutes & committee reports, 1982-1983; Series 7 (Box UP24, Binder 2)
  - Songs of My Family CD, 2007; Series 7 (Box UP24, Folder 3)
  - Jim Holloway's jacket, Series 7 (Box UP24, Item 1)
  - Mayor's Proclamation: Gay Men's Chorus Day, 2001 June 16; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 1)
  - Poster "A little guts & lots of glitter" concert, undated; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 2)
  - Record [LP] presented to Gay Men's Chorus of San Francisco, undated; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 3)
  - Poster from Seattle Men's Chorus holiday concert, undated; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 4)
  - Proclamation from the Mayor of Vancouver as Gay/Lesbian Chorus Day, 1989 July 1; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 5)
  - Certificate of appreciation from Food and Friends, 2008; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 6)
  - Certificate of recognition from the Latino Pride at the DC Center, 2014; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 7)
  - Certificate of appreciation for the Federal City Performing Arts Assoc., 1985; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 8)
  - Poster: Naked Man, My Buddy and Midwest Premiere, 1997; Series 7 (Map-folder 1, Item 9)
  - Framed collage of images, undated; Series 7 (Frame 1)